Paradise released two new pants. They have a zipper and a button and belt holes.
So I'm going to style them today. Let's go.
These are the Ultra pants, so the Ultra version of the regular pants.
So the new pants are called regular because they have these belt loops, they have a zipper, a button,
they have fake pockets, so you can't put anything in these pockets.
here it's just optical illusion and I'm going to show them later in the classic fabric as well
but starting with these ones so I decided to do two looks with each pair of pants a day look and
a night look to go out and the specialty about these pants is that there are two length options
So I'm wearing the tall option and these are wonderful long for people from 172 centimeters on.
And I love that they offer the two length options because, yeah, I need the tall ones.
So for the day look, I decided to do an office chic look.
So a blouse, which is actually a bodysuit.
The hemline can't be pulled out of the trousers because it's a bodysuit.
and I put a really small belt into the belt loops here. You can barely notice it but I think it adds
a lot of dimension to it and yeah the arms are like three quarter and I think it's rather
unusual look for me but I kind of like it. It looks so grown up.
I think I would wear this like um when I would be at the office and there would be like a meeting
with some clients where I had to look chic otherwise I'm just in paradise pants and a hoodie
at the office but if uh something high class would be required that would be my look I would need a
bag like a small one or like the big one for a laptop but other than that um yeah it's a look
and now I'm going to switch to the night look. This is my night look. I got rid of the belt of
the blouse and I changed into a PVC bra, put this cute knitwear top from Nowhere Designs
over the bra. The necklace is also by Nowhere Designs and I put on some very spiky heels
that match great with the metal wear on the top and the necklace. So it's giving a bit
rock star white and if it's like a cold night I do have a jacket a very warm
very cozy jacket I can put on top of it because this is the cutest jacket ever
and it's very fluffy I love this look that's definitely more me than the
office wear look okay showing you the two looks side by side this is the office look or day look
and this is the night look what do you like more I definitely am a fan of this one because more me
but I think the office look is okay as well with the belt we have a use for the belt loops basically
here you could also wear a normal paradise pants without a button and the belt loops so yeah
I think this is really cute but I do have a second pair of pants it's the classic one
and I'm going to change into the first look with these now all right classic aesthetic pants
regular tall version and this is the day look this is how I actually go to the office
just an oversized hoodie or t-shirt and leather look pants is actually my go-to daily look
no kidding and I paired it here with my buffaloes because they're super comfy and super cool
and I just love that oversized plus skinny jeans look and I grew up with skinny jeans
I'm a 90s kid I love skinny jeans I can't do this weird straight leg jeans thingy
there's actually a hack I did here because that hoodie is normally longer but I thought
the belly free look is way better so I just pushed it under my bra in the back and with that
shortened the hoodie because that's the normal length I think it would look better with a normal
paradise pants without belt loops this length but this length is better with the regular pants
Anyway, I'm going to do the night look now.
And I'm back with the night look.
I put on a four-leather bodysuit and belt, which has these kind of tassels and chains
from Nowhere Designs from London.
So and oh yeah, also my Fernando Bellino vonis to give this more of a rocky, rock star vibe.
So here you can see the day look again and of course this is the night look.
I think it's hard to choose one of the two because I would not wear it at the same time.
Basically it's just like I did now, day and night.
But I would wear both of them.
Of course as with all Paradise pants we have the curved seam here on the side
And we also have this second decorative seam here in the back area.
And there is also a denim version available which has real pockets.
So you can put stuff in there.
They aren't that big but they work.
I can show you some pictures.
And also available in two colors, black and blue.
As well as these are available in two materials, the classic and the ultra.
Which one do you prefer?
I think most of the time I prefer the four letter one here and I also love the
denied outfit with the ultra version so it was really cool as well but you can
tell me your favorite outfit in the comments and you can also use my
discount code for paradise and you get 10% off of the whole product range there
was a body suits and dresses a lot of pants colorful pants with or without
zipper and yeah just check it out I'll put all the links down below and I hope
you enjoyed this video I hope I can see you again in the next video check out my
channel here there are more paradise videos if you want to see different
pants and I wish you a nice day bye